Quick links
-----------

    * [
        
        Available on: desktop, mobile and tablet](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/teachyourmonstertoread)

    * [
        
        Available on: desktop, mobile and tablet](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/readingforfun)

    * [
        
        Available on: desktop, mobile and tablet](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/numberskills)

    * [
        
        Available on: desktop, mobile and tablet](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/adventurous-eating)

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

**Teach Your Monster Kids Privacy Notice**
------------------------------------------

**What information do we collect from you?**

We will collect your parent’s or teacher’s name and their email address so that they can set up a Teach Your Monster account.  Your parent or teacher will then add your first name or a nickname to their account so that they can identify you, but no one else can.

We will then collect information about your performance whilst using Teach Your Monster games such as the points you gain and the prizes you are awarded.

**Why do we need this information?**

We need this information so that you can play the Teach Your Monster games.

**How can we use your information?**

We ask your parent or teacher to say 'yes' to creating a Teach Your Monster account and provide information about you.  Saying 'yes' to creating an account is also called 'giving consent'.  As your parent or teacher has said 'yes', we can create a Teach Your Monster account, add you as a student to that account and use your information in the ways that we have explained to your parent or teacher.

**Where do we keep your information?**

We keep your information in databases that we have checked to make sure they are safe.  Your information is protected by a secret code so that it cannot be seen by anyone else without our permission.

**How long do we keep your information for?**

We will keep your information for as long as you continue to play Teach Your Monster games.  We will close accounts if they have not been used for a period of 3 years.

**Who do we share your information with?**

We will never sell or share your data to make money.  We use other companies to help us deliver our game and sometimes they may need access to your information to do this.  We carefully choose these companies, only share with them the information about you that they need to do the work, and we make sure they keep your information safe.

**What are your rights?**

You have the same data protection rights as your parents or teachers.  This includes getting a copy of the information we hold about you, asking us to correct any information we hold about you which is wrong and asking us to delete information we hold about you.  

**Where can you find out more information?**

If you want more information, you can visit our Privacy Policy and Cookies Policy or ask a parent or teacher to contact our Data Protection Officer by contacting [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Teach Your Monster Privacy Policy - full version**
----------------------------------------------------

This privacy policy describes the information we collect and use to support our website and the games and other services we offer, including Teach Your Monster to Read, Teach Your Monster Reading for Fun and Teach Your Monster Number Skills.  Teach Your Monster has a privacy policy for the web-based version of its game service and a privacy policy for the mobile application version of its game service.

**1\. Teach Your Monster (Web-based Version) Privacy Policy**

**2\. Teach Your Monster Mobile Application (iOS and Android) Privacy Policy**

**1\. Teach Your Monster (Web-based Version) Privacy Policy**

**The Basics**

* This site and the games and other services offered through it, the “Game Service”, is intended to be used by teachers and parents/guardians as a reading-related teaching tool for children. (“Students”).
* Teachers and parents/guardians may register on the site, and as a result become “Users”.
* Users may set up individual accounts for their Students, which allow the Students to access, and the User to track Students’ performance in their use of, the Game Service.
* Accounts may only be established by Users, and not by Students themselves; Students must have Users’ permission to use the Game Service.

**Teach Your Monster Limited (we) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and personal data. This Privacy Policy relates to your use of the Teach Your Monster Game Service. As the processing of some data is essential to the functioning of the Game Service if you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy you should not use the Game Service.**

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know what kinds of information we may gather about you (whether you are a User or a Student), how we may use that information, why your information will be used, namely for purposes of the performance of our contract with you as our User, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. Words and phrases used in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as is attributed to them in the [Teach Your Monster User Agreement](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/legals).

This Privacy Policy provides you with certain information that must be provided under the UK General Data Protection Regulation (UK GDPR). This policy primarily covers how we use information relating to our parent/guardian Users who set up accounts on behalf of their own children.  In these cases, we will be the “data controller” for the purposes of data protection law. There are also cases where we will be a “data processor” for the purposes of data protection law.  Where schools, educators and/or teachers set up accounts on behalf of students, we are processing your personal information on behalf of the educator/school/teacher in order that they can provide educational services to their students.  In circumstances where we are a data processor, it is the educator/school/teacher who decides what personal information to collect and how that information is used. Any questions that you may have relating to your personal information and your rights under data protection law should therefore be directed to the school/teacher as the data controller, not to us.

It is important that you read this policy, together with any other privacy notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal information about you, so that you are aware of how and why we are using such information

**Data Protection Principles**

We are required by the UK GDPR to ensure that we follow six principles whilst we are processing your information and it is these principles that are central to our processing procedures.  Your information will be:

* Used lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way;
* Collected only for valid purposes that we have clearly explained to you and not used in any way that is incompatible with those purposes;
* Relevant to the purposes we have told you about and limited only to those purposes;
* Accurate and kept up to date;
* Kept only as long as necessary for the purposes we have told you about; and
* Kept securely.

**Personal information we collect from you**  

Personal data, or personal information as we sometimes call it, means data which relates to an identifiable living person. Users may from time to time provide us with personal data, such as the following:

1. The User’s name and email address – and potentially postal address and telephone number(s);
2. Partial identification information relating to the User’s Student(s), such that the User is able to identify the Student in question, but no-one else would be capable of doing so;
3. Correspondence through the Game Service, and correspondence sent to us by the User;
4. Information based on Students’ activities on and interactions with the Game Service, such as Students’ performance, points gained and prizes awarded; and
5. Information we ask the User to submit to verify identity;
6. Photographs of Students;
7. Information given to us in User feedback surveys;
8. Due to the nature of the service that we provide we do not normally collect “special categories” of sensitive personal data from our Users. Special category information includes; race or ethnicity, religion, sexual orientation, political views, trade union membership and physical or mental health.  In the event you provide us with any special category data, we will take extra care to ensure your rights are protected.

**How is your personal information collected?**

We collect your personal information through different methods including:

* Direct interactions with you via our website, e-mail, phone, User feedback surveys or otherwise.
* Automated technologies or interactions. As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect technical information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal information by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies.
* We may use this automated technology to collect anonymous information about the use of the Game Service. For example, our web server may automatically log which parts of the Game Service Users or Students view, their IP addresses and which web browsers they use. This technology does not identify the User or Student personally, but enables us to compile statistics about the use of the Game Service so we can improve it over time; it also enables us to adapt the Game Service to a Student’s progress and ability.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files which, depending on your browser settings, may be automatically stored on your computer's hard drive when your Web browser accesses a specific Web page.

We use cookies for purposes such as helping us to identify and track visitors’ usage and preferences.

We are of the view that these cookies are not intrusive.

Note that you may not be able to obtain and use an Account on the Game Service, nor will you be able to use certain aspects of the Services, if your browser is set to reject cookies.  
  
You can find out how to manage cookies at this site: [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/)

**Why is your information collected?**

We will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal information in the following circumstances:

* Where you have provided your consent.
* Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
* Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
* Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Your personal information will be collected, processed, stored and used by us, and passed to and processed by our subsidiary and/or affiliated companies and other data processors acting under contract with us for four main purposes:

* To register you as a User
* To provide and promote the Game Service
* To provide customer support
* For research and marketing purposes

We also use your personal information to provide emailed communications. We will retain your personal information only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which the User agrees to under this Privacy Policy and any related agreement(s) with us, or as is required by applicable law, and then we will delete it.

**Email Communications**

By registering as a User and agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you will receive certain emails from us, namely:

* Updates about new features, products and services we make available on or through the Game Service
* News about other games and products or information about literacy that we think will interest Users

Each of the above emails will give you the opportunity of opting-out of receiving future similar communications from us.

In addition, we send emails specifically relating to the usage of the Game Service to Users, such as emails about forgotten passwords, User and Student account activation, and emails which notify Users that a new report on Student progress is available. These emails are intrinsic to the Game Service, and cannot therefore be specifically opted-out of. Should you wish to stop receiving these emails from us, you must de-register as a User.

**Note that we only hold email addresses for Users: we do not send emails to Students.**

**Sharing your personal data**

In our capacity as data controller we will share your personal information with third parties where required by law, where it is necessary to administer the working relationship with you or where we have another legitimate interest in doing so.   

Here is a list of [our third party providers](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/third-party-providers)

Any third parties will be bound by contractual provisions with us and only have access to personal data to perform the described purposes, and may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the UK GDPR.

It is possible that some of the computer systems and companies that process your data on our behalf may be based in countries outside the UK . Countries outside the UK may not have as well developed data protection laws to protect your information as those inside the UK, but we will contractually require that personal data which is processed on our behalf is treated in compliance with UK law and this Privacy Policy.

**Security**

We take appropriate technical and organisational measures to guard against unauthorised or unlawful processing of your personal data and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your personal data. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. We have security measures in place to protect our User and Student database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each User's responsibility:

1. To ensure no-one else uses the Game Service while the User’s machine is "logged on" to the Game Service;
2. To log off or exit from your Account when not using it; and
3. To keep his/her password or other access information secret.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data security breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected breach where we are legally required to do so.

**Marketing with third parties**

We will obtain  your express consent by  opt-in before we share your personal data, with any third party for marketing purposes. Such personal data sharing may include, but is not limited to, information given to us via User feedback surveys.

**What rights do you have?**

Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:

a) Request access to your personal information (commonly known as a "data subject access request"). Once you have made a subject access request we are obliged:

To tell you whether we process any of your personal data.

If so, to provide you with a description of the personal data we hold, the reasons it is being processed, and with whom we share it.

To provide you with a copy of the personal data we process in an intelligible form, and (where this is available) to inform you about the source of the data.

All Subject Access Requests must be in writing to [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 

b) Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.

In order to correct any of the information we hold about you, simply log into your account and make the changes that are required.

c) Request erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal information where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).

d) Object to processing of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes.

e) Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.

f) Request the transfer of your personal information to another party.

If you want to review, verify, correct or request erasure of your personal information, object to the processing of your personal data, or request that we transfer a copy of your personal information to another party, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please note, there are some specific circumstances where these rights do not apply and we can refuse to deal with your request

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal information (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request for access is clearly unfounded or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with the request in such circumstances.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access the information (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is another appropriate security measure to ensure that personal information is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.

**Right to withdraw consent**

In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. To withdraw your consent, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.

**Complaints**

We take any complaints we receive about the collection and use of personal information very seriously.  We would encourage you to bring it to our attention if you think that our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate.  You can make a complaint at any time by contacting us (see contact details section below).

If you think our collection or use of personal information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate or if you have concerns about the security of your personal information, you also have the right to make a complaint to the Information Commissioner’s Office.  You can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office at the following address:

Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF

Contact us:

You can e-mail us at contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write to us at the following address TYM Ltd, 83-85 Saffron Hill, London EC1N 8RT.

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of England and Wales.

**2\. Teach Your Monster Mobile Application (iOS and Android) Privacy Policy**

**The Basics**

* This site and the games and other services offered through it, the “Game Service”, is intended to be used by teachers and parents/guardians as a reading-related teaching tool for children. (“Students”).
* Teachers and parents/guardians may register on the site, and as a result become “Users”.
* Users may set up individual accounts for their Students, which allow the Students to access, and the User to track Students’ performance in their use of, the Game Service.
* Accounts may only be established by Users, and not by Students themselves; Students must have Users’ permission to use the Game Service.

**Teach Your Monster Limited (we) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and personal data. This Privacy Policy relates to your use of the Teach Your Monster mobile application software (the App). As the processing of some data is essential to the functioning of the App if you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy you should not use the App.**

This privacy policy aims to give you information about how we collect and process your personal information through your use of the App (whether you are using the Standard Mode or Login Mode).  It makes you aware of how and why your personal information will be used, namely for the purposes of the performance of our contract with you as our User, and how long it will usually be retained for. It provides you with certain information that must be provided under the UK General Data Protection Regulation (UK GDPR). This policy primarily covers how we use information relating to our parent/guardian Users who set up accounts on behalf of their own children.  In these cases, we will be the “data controller” for the purposes of data protection law. There are also cases where we will be a “data processor” for the purposes of data protection law.  Where educators, teachers or schools set up accounts on behalf of students, we are processing your personal information on behalf of the school/teacher in order that they can provide educational services to their students.  In circumstances where we are a data processor, it is the educator/school/teacher who decides what personal information to collect and how that information is used. Any questions that you may have relating to your personal information and your rights under data protection law should therefore be directed to the school/teacher as the data controller, not to us.

It is important that you read this policy, together with any other privacy notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal information about you, so that you are aware of how and why we are using such information

**Scope**

The App works in tandem with the website www.teachyourmonster.org (the Website) which is run and operated by “Teach Your Monster Ltd (“TYM Ltd”). We may share data with TYM Ltd in the circumstances set out below and any data processed by TYM Ltd will be processed in accordance with the Website’s privacy policy below or at www.teachyourmonster.org/legals. Game progress may be transferred between the App and the Website.

In this Privacy Policy the terms ‘you’, ‘your’ and ‘yours’ refer to both 1) the Device Owner (being either the owner of the device on which the App has been downloaded or the owner of the account used to purchase the App and 2) the player of the game on the App (if different).

In order to make use of the App the Device Owner must accept these terms. As the App has been developed to be played by children who are minors, the Device Owner will be accepting this Privacy Policy on behalf of the child player. In these circumstances the Device Owner represents that he or she is either the parent or legal guardian of any child who is using the App.

**Data Protection Principles**

We are required by the UK GDPR to ensure that we follow six principles whilst we are processing your information and it is these principles that are central to our processing procedures.  Your information will be:

* Used lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way;
* Collected only for valid purposes that we have clearly explained to you and not used in any way that is incompatible with those purposes;
* Relevant to the purposes we have told you about and limited only to those purposes;
* Accurate and kept up to date;
* Kept only as long as necessary for the purposes we have told you about; and
* Kept securely.

**Information We May Collect From You.**

You may give us information about yourself when using the App or communicating with us about the App. Some of this may be Personal data, or personal information as we sometimes call it, which means data which relates to an identifiable living person.

When you use the App we will automatically collect the following non-personal data:

A set of data which encapsulates a player’s progress through the game, the rewards they’ve collected, the design of the player’s monster and other information to provide continuity of the App experience (Saved Data); and we may collect

Technical information, including the type of mobile device you use, a unique device identifier (for example, your Device's IMEI number), mobile network information, your mobile operating system (Device Information);

We will collect the following personal data:-

Standard Mode (Standard Mode enables you to set up players within the app). When creating a player we will ask you for the player’s first name. This name and the player’s Saved Data will be stored within the App. No other personal information will be requested or stored. Although not requested or required, the Device Owner or player may disclose more personal information, such as a surname, and this will be stored in the app.

Login Mode - login mode enables you to log into the App using an existing account and utilising a player’s credentials that have been previously set up on the Website. The player’s name and progress made in the Website version of the game will be transferred to the App to enable the continuation of play with that account through the App. Progress in the App will become Saved Data which will periodically be sent back to the Website in order to save that player’s progress. No additional types of personally identifiable information will be added when this data is sent.

Any personal data provided by you via the Website prior to using Login Mode in the App will be governed by the Website’s privacy policy below or at www.teachyourmonster.org/legals

Additionally, you may give us information about you if you corresponded with us (for example via email), take part in our User feedback surveysor report a problem with the App or our services. Any correspondence or reporting should be done by the Device Owner.

**Cookies & Uses Made of the Information**

Saved Data will be stored within the App and periodically this data and/or the Device Information may be sent to the Website servers and stored for the purposes of analytics. The player’s name will be stripped from this data and no additional data will be sent to the server by the App when using the Standard Mode. Saved Data will be sent to the Website when using Login Mode to allow for continuity of game play via the Website version of the game.

**Why do we collect your information?**

We will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

* Where you have given us consent
* Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
* Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
* Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Your personal data will be collected, processed, stored and used by us, and passed to and processed by our subsidiary and/or affiliated companies and other data processors acting under contract with us for five main purposes:

* To register you as a User
* To provide and promote the App Service
* To provide customer support
* To process in-App purchases
* For research and marketing purposes

We will retain your personal data only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which the Device Owner consents under this Privacy Policy and any related agreement(s) with us, or as is required by applicable law, and then we will delete it.

**Disclosure of your Information**

In our capacity as data controller we will share your personal information with third parties where required by law, where it is necessary to administer the working relationship with you or where we have another legitimate interest in doing so.   We may disclose some or all of the data we collect from you when you download or use the App to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company (where applicable) and its subsidiaries (as defined in section 1159 of the Companies Act 2006) and to TYM Ltd who operates the Website and any personal data shared with TYM Ltd will be processed in accordance with the Website’s privacy policy below or at www.teachyourmonster.org/legals

Any third parties will be bound by contractual provisions with us and only have access to personal data to perform the described purposes, and may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the UK GDPR.

Payment information for in-App purchases will be managed through the payment system of the relevant third-party App store provider and is therefore subject to the parental controls of the relevant device being used to access our App. Payment information will not be stored by us on our App. 

**Marketing with third parties**

We will obtain your express consent by opt-in before we share your personal data, with any third party for marketing purposes. Such personal data sharing may include, but is not limited to, information given to us via User feedback surveys.

**Where We Store Your Personal Data**

Saved Data will be stored locally within the App on your device and may be transferred and stored on the Website’s servers.

Where data is stored on the Website servers it shall be processed by TYM Ltd in accordance with the Website’s privacy policy below (or at www.teachyourmonster.org) It is possible that some of the computer systems and companies that process your data on behalf of TYM Ltd may be based in countries outside the UK. Countries outside the UK may not have as well developed data protection laws to protect your information as those inside the UK, but TYM Ltd will contractually require that personal data which is processed on its behalf is treated in compliance with UK law and the privacy policy on the Website.

**External Websites**

The App may from time to time, contain links to external websites. These will be protected by an adult check.

If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any personal data that may be collected through these websites or services, such as contact and location data. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites or use these services.

**Security**

We take appropriate technical and organisational measures to guard against unauthorised or unlawful processing of your personal information and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your personal data. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our App reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. We have security measures in place to protect our User and Student database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each User's responsibility:

1. To ensure no-one else uses the App Service while the User’s device is "logged on" to the Game Service;
2. To log off or exit from your Account when not using it; and
3. To keep his/her password or other access information secret.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data security breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected breach where we are legally required to do so.

**What rights do you have?**

Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:

1. Request access to your personal information (commonly known as a "data subject access request"). Once you have made a subject access request we are obliged:

To tell you whether we process any of your personal data

If so, to provide you with a description of the personal data we hold, the reasons it is being processed, and with whom we share it

To provide you with a copy of the personal data we process in an intelligible form, and (where this is available) to inform you about the source of the data

All Subject Access Requests must be in writing to [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

1. Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.

In order to correct any of the information we hold about you, simply log into your account and make the changes that are required.

1. Request erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal information where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).
2. Object to processing of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
3. Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
4. Request the transfer of your personal information to another party.

If you want to review, verify, correct or request erasure of your personal information, object to the processing of your personal data, or request that we transfer a copy of your personal information to another party, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please note, there are some specific circumstances where these rights do not apply and we can refuse to deal with your request

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal information (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request for access is clearly unfounded or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with the request in such circumstances.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access the information (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is another appropriate security measure to ensure that personal information is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.

**Right to withdraw consent**

Where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. To withdraw your consent, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.

**Complaints**

We take any complaints we receive about the collection and use of personal information very seriously.  We would encourage you to bring it to our attention if you think that our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate.  You can make a complaint at any time by contacting us (see contact details section below).

If you think our collection or use of personal information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate or if you have concerns about the security of your personal information, you also have the right to make a complaint to the Information Commissioner’s Office.  You can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office at the following address:

Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF

**Contact us**

You can e-mail us at contact [\[email protected\]](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write to us at the following address TYM Ltd, 83-85 Saffron Hill, London EC1N 8RT.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes we may make to this privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you when you next start the App. The new terms may be displayed on-screen and you may be required to read and accept them to continue your use of the App or the Services.

**Governing law**

This policy is governed by the laws of England and Wales.

### Follow us!

Sign up for more Monster News!
------------------------------

Free newsletter full of news, resources, activities, printables and exclusive offers.

Email

By subscribing, you agree to Teach Your Monster's [Terms of Use](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/legals), our [Privacy Policy](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/privacy-policy) and receiving emails from Teach Your Monster.

##### 🍪 We use cookies

Cookies help us deliver our services. By using our services, you agree to our use of cookies.

OK [Learn More](https://www.teachyourmonster.org/legals)
